Hey, Michel!
What?!
You're riding way too fast tonight!
If you don't want to die,
you better slow down!
Michel!
The sound of the wind is
exceptionally sweet tonight!
There's no way I'm stopping!
Y-You want a race?! Bastard!
Ah... This rain sucks, doesn't it?
So, who are you waiting for? Your boyfriend?
You're going to freeze
if you hang around here.
Hey, why don't you forget
your boyfriend, come with me,
and I'll find us a warm place
where I can buy you dinner?
Great!
H-Hey!
Wait up!
What's going on here?
There's nothing here.
Is that what you think?
Wh-What's going on here?!
Why, have you forgotten?
That's insensitive of you...
...considering you're the
very man responsible for this.
Recently, there have been a string of
women going missing in Elanay City, you know.
Each one of them was picked up
by some guy and treated to dinner,
then spent a night with him at a hotel,
and ultimately went missing when he
brought them to this abandoned building.
Come on... you think I did this?
Give me a break. Do I look like the kind of
human being who'd do something like that?
No... You don't look like a human being.
I prefer you in this form!
Impressive skills.
Who are you guys?
We represent the Highway Department.
We've been searching for you for some time.
The highly-skilled female Devil Hunter
who takes out any adversary without fail,
Miss Lady.
--Your real na...
--What do you want?
We've got a job for you.
Unbelievable! Guys' places are such a mess!
No one's going to want to come to
a sty like this, much less any clients...
Mr. Dante!
A guest! Hello!
One basil and spicy salami
pizza, no olives...
Thanks. I'll pay you everything
I owe at the end of the month.
Pizza again?
When do you think clients will start coming?
I suppose I probably
better decorate the outside too.
Give me a break.
You saw the pizza boy's reaction, didn't you?
None of the people who would come
here can appreciate your fancy tastes.
Just put everything back the way it was ASAP.
Welcome!
Hmmm...
Dante, it seems like your sense of style
has improved a lot since we last met.
I see...
And you must be Patty Lowell.
Huh? How do you know?
Am I famous or something?
The little girl hanging
around the Devil May Cry
has become quite the
subject of gossip in this town...
But it's not like you came all this way
just to have a look at this brat, now is it?
What are you here for?
If it's about some job,
thanks, but no thanks.
Cold as always...
It's 'cause the jobs you
bring to me are always shit.
That's a fine way to talk.
Are you aware of how much
money you owe me? Don't you get it?
One of my purposes today
is to collect what you owe me.
Maybe you're the one who doesn't get it.
I'm so deep in debt with
you I can't even keep track.
Obviously I can't pay it all back right now.
Well, I was aware of that at
any rate. What can you do?
How about this, then?
How about a bet? If I put the 8-ball in,
you take the job I got for you unconditionally.
You game?
You can never do things
the simple way, can you?
It's a deal.
And if you miss, you forgive my
debt and pay me 20,000 in cash.
Done.
That was amazing!
Shit. All right...
Dammit.
You should just be a hustler.
You'd make more cash, don't you think?
Just hitting a ball doesn't do it for me.
I have a need to annihilate and destroy.
Well, who's the poor wretch this time?
Devils... of course.
What the hell is this?
These morons can't be the
devils you were talking about....
Look.
As far as the Highway Department is
concerned, these guys are real devils.
Quit messing with me!
Why would a "Devil Hunter" waste
time taking out a bunch of bikers?
That's why I'm giving the job
to a jack-of-all-trades like you.
Because I don't know what the
Highway Department was thinking,
but they came to me with the job.
The hell with this.
I'm going home.
Huh? What's wrong?
I can't use swords or guns
when dealing with humans.
In a way, they're a bigger pain
to deal with than actual devils.
What's more, they won't
listen to a word I say.
Who needs words or weapons to deal with them?
Follow me.
Well... Is he here yet?
No luck.
Might as well just forget about it.
What?! I dare you to say that again!
Hey!
Who do you think you are, honey?
I'm not interested in talking to
you guys. Where's your leader?
What the hell is your problem?
I'm Vincent, the leader. What do you want?
I'm sorry, would you guys
mind leaving this place?
What are you talking about?
We do what we want, where we want!
See? Like I said... Talking to those losers,
who don't even know what a pain
in the ass they are, is a waste of time.
What did you say?!
Hang on. I'm sorry about
the inconvenience to you guys,
but would you let us do our thing for now?
There's a guy I'm looking
for that I have to fight.
My older brother ran against him
three weeks ago and got killed.
This guy's a legend on the highway, and
everyone who's run against him is dead.
I have to avenge my brother!
What a bunch of nonsense...
Your brother getting himself killed
racing others around is dumb enough.
But you're even dumber
for trying to get revenge.
What'd you say?!
Wait. If you want to pick a fight
with this guy, why not race him?
Huh?
If you lose, you leave this place quietly.
Hey, Lady! What do you think you're doing?
It's fine, isn't it?
If you win, your job's finished.
The money will be yours.
Wait a damn minute! I'm not...
This guy you're talking about,
his name's "Red Eye," correct?
If you race him, this Red Eye
guy will probably show up.
You...
Here you go.
I don't need it.
Didn't think so.
Me either!
H-Hey!
That's crazy!
You... What are you up to?
Don't say it like that.
I'm just trying to take care of you
so you don't end up starving to death.
Shit... In for a penny, in for a pound.
I guess I'll stick around a little longer.
Here, I probably won't be needing this.
Probably not. For now, at least...
How do you like that?
Dammit!
You're going to have a hard time
avenging your brother if you ride that slow.
Shiiiit!
Take that! This race is all mine!
He's got nitros! Idiot!
Brother!
Wait! Don't go!
Stop!
Brother! Brother! Brother!
There's no way I can stop!
Not when the wind's this good!
This sound, eh?
What are you trying to accomplish,
going so far to follow your brother?
That woman... This is what
she had planned all along.
Fine then!
Shit!
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
You called me 'cause you knew you wouldn't
be able to take this thing out, didn't you?!
Well, if you already know what's going
on, why don't you just go get that guy?
You make it sound like it's so easy.
What's wrong? Is it too difficult for you?
Nope, easy as can be!
Speeding causes accidents!
Brother...
Brother!
You had planned to use me all along.
Sorry. Actually this was the real job the
Highway Department wanted to have done.
You can never do things
the simple way, can you?
And you can't ever simply do what I ask you.
Damn straight.
Brother!
Brother...
Even with this room put back the
way it was, I still don't see any clients.
I'm all about a one-day workweek.
I should be getting paid for
that recent job any day now...
Recent job... You mean the
devil on the motorcycle thing?
Yep. After all, I ended up
getting rid of the Highway Devil.
Lady's negotiating with the
guys from the Highway Department
trying get us a big wad of cash.
Here we go!
I was waiting to hear from
you! Oh, about my money...
What?
You added to my debt?
Yes. We got paid for taking care of Red Eye,
but there are some charges for
repairing that bridge you tore up...
I'm pretty sure the bill will come to you.
What? Our pay?
I'll deduct it from what
you owe me, naturally.
What? Just a dang minute!
Shit! That woman...
I guess you're just an unlucky guy.
Shut up.
Here you go!
That woman told me that your office was here,
so I thought I'd drop by to say "thanks."
Thank you.
If I had kept on like I was, I'd be dead too.
For some reason I thought I heard
the voice of my brother saying,
"It'd be a waste for you to die."
I'm done chasing the
remembrance of my brother.
From here on I ride for me...
And that's why I gotta ask.
Would you race me one more time?
Let's make a little bet.
A bet?
If none of the balls go in, I'll race you.
But if I sink the 8-ball...
Yeah?
You buy me dinner.
There are people out there who would say
that there's nothing more important than love.
But is love really that great?
There are women who, because
of love, get chased around by men.
And there are men who,
because of love, get killed by women.
To boil it down, for love to be so great,
there's gotta be something else
behind it that's even greater.
But I'm not going to
tell you what that is.
I'm not that unsophisticated.